# JASON NELSON

377 New Milford Avenue, Dumont, NJ 07628 Home: 201-384-3828 Cell: 347-792-9311 Jasonnelson11@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced Customer Service Representative with excellent client and project management skills. Dedicated to building customer loyalty and promoting win-win results for the company and the client. Action-oriented with strong ability to communicate effectively with technology, executive, and business audiences. Full stack web developer continuously learning the new tech being applied in the technologic field today.

### **SKILLS**

- First Contact Resolution focused
- Report generation and analysis
- Results-oriented
- Experience in working in a fast-paced environment
- CSS3
- BootStrap
- API's
- Github and Git Version Control
- DOM Manipulation

- Continuous improvement
- Windows skilled
- Technology savvy
- Multitasker
- HTML5
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Ajax
- Git Bash, Command Prompt, and Terminal
- FTP Client (Firezilla)

### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Rutgers Coding Bootcamp, Jersey City, NJ, United States

2018-2019

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - COMPUTER SCIENCE

Montclair State University, Montclair, NJ, United States

2017-2018

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HOMESENSE PARAMUS, NJ 2018-CURRENT

Loss Prevention Customer Service Associate

Responsible for deterring shoplifters and greeting the customers as they walk in.

- Audit departments throughout the store
- Write reports
- Grade department personnel on their ability to control shrinkage (loss of merchandise)
- Train staff on loss prevention strategies
- Ensure store personnel do all they can to control theft

HOMESENSE PARAMUS, NJ 2018-2018

#### SALES ASSOCIATE

Responsible for the maintenance of the store and providing excellent customer service.

- Keeping the selling floor stocked with merchandise.
- Showing outstanding selling skills
- Demonstrate product knowledge by reading current vendor tags and pamphlets.

Domino's Pizza Dumont, NJ

2016 то 2018

# **Customer Service Representative**

Considered a veteran staff agent, responsible for assisting in the overall operations and organization of the department.

- Responsible for daily operational duties
- Training of new staff and managers
- Direct management of inbound call and order taking
- In charge of customer grievance resolution
- Directed shift peak times during management absence
- Responsible for pizza preparation